<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<resources>
    <string-array name="gesture">
        <item>Bicep Curl</item>
        <item>Resistance Band</item>
        <item>Tricep Extension</item>
        <item>Tricep Kickbacks</item>
        <item>Tricep Push Downs</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="gesture_desc">
        <item>This exercise varies the angle of the shoulder</item>
        <item>This exercise works the tricep muscle. </item>
        <item>This exercise strengthens the Triceps Brachii muscle.</item>
        <item>This exercise is a mid-stage rehab exercise.</item>
        <item>This exercise can be performed with a band</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="gesture_details">
        <item>The upper arm is supported just above the elbow by the back of the other hand, whilst
            the athlete bends the elbow against the resistance of the weight.
            Performing the exercise with a larger degree of elbow flexion works the long head of the biceps more.
            Performing this exercise with the palm facing up works the Biceps Brachii, with the palm
            down emphasizes the Brachialis and with the thumb upwards, focuses on the Brachioradialis.
        </item>
        <item>Place the centre of the band under your feet and hold one end in each hand.
        Start with the ams behind your head, elbows pointing to the ceiling.
        Straighten the arms overhead.
        </item>
        <item>The starting position is lying on the back with the elbow bent and pointing to the celieing as shown.
            The elbow is the straightened, listing the weight up above the head.
            The weight is then carefully lowered back down to the shoulder.
        </item>
        <item>Stand with one end of the band under the feet and the other end in one hand.
            Lean forwards at the hip, keeping the back straight.
            Start with the arm bent at the elbow, wrist at chest level.
            Straighten the arm out behind you.
        </item>
        <item>The band is anchored to a high point and one end held in each hand.
            The athlete starts with their elbows bent and then straightens them against the resistance of the band.
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <array name="gesture_picture">
        <item>@drawable/bicepcurl</item>
        <item>@drawable/resistancebandtricepextension</item>
        <item>@drawable/triceprxtensionsupine</item>
        <item>@drawable/tricepkickbackswithband</item>
        <item>@drawable/triceppushdowns</item>
    </array>
</resources>