<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<resources>
    <string-array name="places">
        <item>Inner Arm Stretch</item>
        <item>Elbow Stretch</item>
        <item>Crawling Stretch</item>
        <item>Elbow Weight Training</item>
        <item>Seated Pushup</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="place_desc">
        <item> Place your hands palms down on the table and rotate your wrist.</item>
        <item>The elbow stretch focuses on restoring a range of motion to the elbow.</item>
        <item>Gently lean your body backwards, keeping your arm position, until you feel a stretch.</item>
        <item>Gently bend and straighten the elbow.</item>
        <item>Sultan Ahmed Mosque is mosque locates in Istabul, Turkey</item>
        <item>Table Mountain is mountain and park locates in Cape Town, South Africa.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="place_details">
        <item>For this exercise, place your hands palms down on the table and rotate your wrist
            so your fingers point towards your body. Keeping your elbows straight, slowly move
            your body backwards until you feel a stretch on the inside of the arm. Lean on the
            table for support if you need to.
        </item>
        <item>The elbow stretch focuses on restoring a range of motion to the elbow. This exercise
            can be done while sitting or standing. Hold the arm at a comfortable position,
            then carefully bend and straighten the elbows as if you are doing a dumbbell curl.
        </item>
        <item>Take up a crawling position with your elbows straight. Gently lean your body
            backwards, keeping your arm position, until you feel a stretch on your inner arm.
            Hold the position and repeat.
        </item>
        <item>In a standing or sitting position, hold a small weight in your hand. Gently bend
            and straighten the elbow. Repeat to your endurance point. Over time, increase
            repetitions as the elbow strengthens.
        </item>
        <item>Finally, sit on the ground with your knees bent and your palms on the floor,
            keeping your fingers pointing forward. Push through your hands to cause your bottom
            to lift off the floor slightly. Repeat as you grow stronger.
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <array name="places_picture">
        <item>@drawable/innerarmstretch</item>
        <item>@drawable/elbowstretch</item>
        <item>@drawable/crawlingstretch</item>
        <item>@drawable/elbowstretch</item>
        <item>@drawable/seatedpushup</item>
    </array>
</resources>